

# Phạm Vũ Quang Minh

## Talent Acquisition and Development

Date of birth: January, 02, 1995

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 0772341188

Email: phamvuquangminh1995@gmail.com

Address: No 1162, 1A Highway, Tan Tao A Ward, Binh Tan

District, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Website: Skype ID: phamvuquangminh1995@gmail.com

### **OBJECTIVE**

I want to challenge myself in an active and professional environment and have opportunities to bring a lot of value to customers. In the next 3 years, I want to practice and develop specialized skills in the field of human resources. With my experience and enthusiasm, I am confident that I can complete the work assigned and please customers from that I will contribute to the development of your company.

#### **EDUCATION**

September, 2015 - July, 2019 H

Ho Chi Minh City University of Foreign Languages - Information

**Technology (HUFLIT)** 

Deparment: International Business Administration

Major: Human Resource Management

August, 2012 - June, 2015

Chu Van An highschool

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

September 2019 - January 2021 OPPO - Authorized Exclusive Distributor Vietnam

**Product Trainer** 

Training (40%)

- Develop a schedule to assess training needs
- Consult with other trainers, managers, and leadership
- Communicate training needs and online resources
- Create training strategies, initiatives, and materials
- Contact and utilize outside vendors and resources for instructional technology
- Test and review created materials
- Maintain a database of all training materials
- Instruct employee training and onboarding
- Conduct training through new materials
- Coordinate and monitor enrollment, schedules, costs, and equipment
- Training information and feature of the new products to internal employees and partners

Quality Controlling (30%)

- Review employee performance and learning
- Ensure Sale teams comply with the working regulations
- Control offline and online activities of Sale team consistent with

#### corporate culture

#### Internal Relation (20%)

- Plan to organize activities that connect the employee's work spirit
- Control costs and materials of activities
- Evaluate the effectiveness of the program
- Organize team-building activities, kich-off event

#### Recruitment (10%)

- Sourcing and attracting candidates by using databases, social media, etc.
- Conducting interviews and filtering candidates for open positions.

#### June 2019 - August 2019

#### **Adecco Vietnam**

Recruitment Intern

Main responsibilities:

- Source and recruit candidates by using databases, social media, etc Screen candidates resumes and job applications
- Conduct interviews using various reliable recruiting and selection tools/methods to filter candidates within schedule
- Assess applicants' relevant knowledge, skills, soft skills, experience, and aptitudes
- Onboard new employees to become fully integrated
- Monitor and apply HR recruiting best practices
- Update internal databases with new employee information, including contact details and employment forms
- Schedule and confirm interviews with candidates

#### November, 2017 - June, 2018

#### Vietnam-Australia Society Academy (V.A.S.A)

Sale Consultant

Main responsibilities:

- Advise, share and explain to customers about the content of the program, courses and sales policy of the center
- Maintaining and developing potential customers in the business of the Company
- Collaborate with relevant departments to conduct seminars, center events or corporate events and test sessions for students.
- Update information about customers, search and reach customers to consult/sell courses
- Perform administrative tasks, manage training classes

## November, 2016 - October 2017 Vietnam-Australia Society Academy (V.A.S.A)

**Teaching Assistant** 

Main responsibilities:

- Support in managing class and follow provided lesson plan
- Guide students to do homework

- Monitor and evaluate the learning process of students
- Carry out customer service as requested

## **ACTIVITIES**

August, 2016 - January, 2020

"Under Tree's Shadow" charity project

English tutor for children

- Guide children study English in activities and lessons
- Support to organize science classes

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

2018	Microsoft Office Specialist (MOS) for Word and Excel
2017	Top 30 CV Contest
2016	Public Speaking Art course at Youth Culture Center

## **SKILLS**

Language	English
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint

## **INTERESTS**

I like reading books such as You Can Negotiate Anything, You Can Read Anyone. I am interested in finding approaches to improve human performance and motivate members to increase productivity.

## **REFERENCES**

References available upon request